{"id": 0, "tokens": ["Gully", "cricket", "chal", "raha", "hain", "yaha", "\"", "(", "Soniya", ")", "Gandhi", "\""], "ner_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PERSON", "O", "B-PERSON", "O"]}
{"id": 1, "tokens": ["I", "liked", "a", "@YouTube", "video", "https://t.co/DmVqhZbdaI", "Kabhi", "Palkon", "Pe", "Aasoon", "Hai-", "Kishore", "Kumar", "-Vocal", "Cover", "By", "Stephen", "Qadir"], "ner_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PERSON", "I-PERSON", "O", "O", "O", "B-PERSON", "I-PERSON"]}
{"id": 2, "tokens": ["RT", "@rameshchahal", ":", "@Gurmeetramrahim", "#MSG2In505crOn200thDay", "Superb", ".......", "guru", "pa", "...."], "ner_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": 3, "tokens": ["RT", "@nitibnsl", ":", "#DSSFoundationDay", "swarg", "Dharti", "par", "dekhna", "hai", "to", "ek", "visit", "Dera", "Sacha", "Sauda", "at", "Sirsa", "ki", "ho", "Jaaye", "https://t.co/e8Tj1HRPjt"], "ner_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PLACE", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": 4, "tokens": ["@RoflGandhi_", "itna", "hone", "ke", "baad", "bhi", "airtel", "se", "port", "kyu", "nahi", "kar", "lete", "dada", "??", "Idea", "ka", "ad", "ab", "abhishek", "bachchan", "nahi", "kar", "raha", "..!!"], "ner_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORGANISATION", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORGANISATION", "O", "O", "O", "B-PERSON", "I-PERSON", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": 5, "tokens": ["1100", "yrs", "old", "Bhagwan", "Brahma", "from", "Cambodia", ".", "Combodia", "was", "also", "a", "prominent", "#IndianizedKingdoms", ".", "#HinduismAbroad", "https://t.co/jCJBDOdqsU"], "ner_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PERSON", "O", "B-PLACE", "O", "B-PLACE", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": 6, "tokens": ["RT", "@sarvjot19972", ":", "#MSGmissionHumanity", "guru", "ji", "passion", "again", "help", "people"], "ner_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": 7, "tokens": ["'", "Ghar", "wapsi", "'", "of", "world", "cup", "#CWC15Final", "#Australia"], "ner_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": 8, "tokens": ["@ArvindKejriwal", "@SirJadeja", "aapka", "kam", "hai", "cricket", "khlna", "cricket", "kheliye", "agr", "aapko", "politician", "ki", "trah", "tweet", "krna", "hai", "to", "pahle", "politics", "me", "aaiye"], "ner_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": 9, "tokens": ["RT", "AAP_Najafgarh", "\"", "RT", "INarendra7", ":", ".", "ArvindKejriwal", "on", "the", "Stage", "#HopeOfPunjabKejriwal", "AamAadmiParty", "https://t.co/Ah8vFrenfE", "\""], "ner_tags": ["O", "B-ORGANISATION", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PERSON", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": 10, "tokens": ["RT", "@AskAnshul", ":", "look", "Audience", "applauds", "when", "Pak", "call", "Hindu", "Kutta", "n", "@SitaramYechury", "sees", "nothing", "wrong", "in", "chanting", "Pakistan", "Zindabad", "https", ":/"], "ner_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PLACE", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PLACE", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": 11, "tokens": ["*", "Kohli", "and", "Dhawan", "crying", "*", "Dhoni", ":", "Kya", "hua", "?", "Kohli", ":", "Yaar", "we", "just", "asked", "Raina's", "saalis", "to", "return", "shoes", ".", "They", "said", "#WontGiveItBack"], "ner_tags": ["O", "B-PERSON", "O", "B-PERSON", "O", "O", "B-PERSON", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PERSON", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PERSON", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": 12, "tokens": ["@Muzammalafzal", "Pardesiaa", "eid", "ty", "jaa", "ryan", "ghar", "??", "@NabeelFaryal"], "ner_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": 13, "tokens": ["Aaj", "hi", "school", "khula", "aur", "shahjade", "saab", "gayab", "....", "bhai", "gazab", "student", "hai", ".", "#RahulOnLeave"], "ner_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": 14, "tokens": ["@Ashishtics", "tou", "mein", "kounsa", "uspenfilm", "banane", "wala", "hu", "@Obnoxious_Ravan"], "ner_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": 15, "tokens": ["RT", "@arshi_yasin", ":", "These", "are", "not", "dead", "bodies", ",", "they", "are", "our", "living", "farmers", ".", "These", "are", "farmers", "protesting", "at", "Nashik", ",", "Maharashtra", ".", "https://t.co/"], "ner_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PLACE", "O", "B-PLACE", "O", "O"]}
{"id": 16, "tokens": ["#WhereIsRahul", "trending", "@1", "Rahul-Accha", "ji", "aaj", "meri", "badi", "yaad", "aa", "rahi", "hai", "...", "Election", "k", "time", "to", "Rahul", "ne", "khayi", "CandyBar", "abki", "baar", "ModiSarkar", ".."], "ner_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PERSON", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORGANISATION", "O"]}
{"id": 17, "tokens": ["@P2makodo", "btw", "ye", "aunty", "kon", "hai", "?"], "ner_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": 18, "tokens": ["Teacher", ":", "Pakistan", "will", "win", "15th", "Feb", "match", ".", "Which", "tense", "it", "is", "?", "Pakistani", "Child", ":", "Future", "Impossible", "Tense", "#IndWins", "#RIPEnglish", "#Indians"], "ner_tags": ["O", "O", "B-PLACE", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": 19, "tokens": ["#RahulOnLeave", "he", "is", "preparing", "for", "2019", ".", "leher", "ke", "baad", "bunda", "bandi", "Apki", "baar", "Rahul", "gandhi", ".", "ws", "modiji", "ki", "man", "ki", "baat", "samajh", "lega", "bina", "bole", "."], "ner_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PERSON", "I-PERSON", "O", "O", "B-PERSON", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": 20, "tokens": ["now", "we", "can", "say", "strong", "..", "#WontGiveItBack", "ab", "bi", "nahi", "phodenke", "yaar", "....", "#IndvsPak", "#CWC15", "@ICC"], "ner_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": 21, "tokens": ["@Gurmeetramrahim", "thank", "u", "sweeet", "sweeeet", "papa", "ji"], "ner_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": 22, "tokens": ["@aditiraohydari", "@NimratOfficial", "happy", "bday", "nimrat", "kaur"], "ner_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PERSON", "I-PERSON"]}
{"id": 23, "tokens": ["I'm", "at", "Sultanahmet", "(", "Istanbul", ",", "Trkiye", ")", "w/", "18", "others", "[", "pic", "]:", "http://t.co/WaRZaQJbIF"], "ner_tags": ["O", "O", "B-PLACE", "O", "B-PLACE", "O", "B-PLACE", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": 24, "tokens": ["#5SaalKejriwal", "..", "Even", "Pakistanis", "r", "Celebrating", "AK49", "..", "HaHaHa", "..", "Ye", "bhi", "Mile", "Hue", "Hai", "Ji", "..", "#DelhiDecides", "http://t.co/eRi6gPgFSQ"], "ner_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": 25, "tokens": ["Uska", "dimple", "Mere", "header", "ko", "khoobsurat", "karaha"], "ner_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": 26, "tokens": ["RT", "@ggiittiikkaa", ":", "Ab", "toh", "Mark", "Zuckerberg", "bhi", "Jaahil", "Sanghi", "Bigot", "Troll", "ho", "gaya", ".", "Koi", "aisa", "karta", "hai", "bhalaa", "?", "#BurnolLagaoLibtardsBachao", "htt"], "ner_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PERSON", "I-PERSON", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": 27, "tokens": ["RT", "@DOCTORATLARGE", ":", "Reason", "I", "hate", "Kejriwal", "the", "most", ":", "Other", "politicians", "are", "devils", "pretending", "to", "be", "people", ",", "while", "Kejriwal", "is", "a", "devil", "pretend"], "ner_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PERSON", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PERSON", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": 28, "tokens": ["Kabi", "Sath", "Deny", "K", "Waday", ",", "Kabi", "Bhool", "Jane", "Ki", "Qasmain", ".....!!", ":", ":", "Mujhe", "Aj", "Tak", "Pta", "Na", "Chala", ",", "K", "Tum", "Majbur", "Ho", "?", "Ya", "Magrur", "......", ":')"], "ner_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": 29, "tokens": ["@iamlakshmirai", "ohmm", "namashivaya", "#MahaShivratri", "wishes", ":(", "sister"], "ner_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": 30, "tokens": ["Kejriwal", "and", "Sisodia", "to", "join", "Anna", "for", "Dharna", ".", "February", "to", "khatam", "hone", "dete", "mere", "bhai", ".", "#AnnaReturns", "#RahulOnLeave"], "ner_tags": ["B-PERSON", "O", "B-PERSON", "O", "O", "B-PERSON", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": 31, "tokens": ["#Mahashivratri", "Radiant", "Shakti", "-", "Tripura", "Sundari", "Goddess", "of", "#Awakening", "via", "@saileshvora55", "http://t.co/T9THydo6Yq"], "ner_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PLACE", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": 32, "tokens": ["#INDvsPAK", "#Afridi", "Afridi", ":", "out", "ni", "hue", "hmm", ",", "sheed", "hue", "hm", "Dhoni", ":", "tum", "to", "paida", "hi", "chudne", "ko", "hue", "o", ",", "chahe", "match", "ho", "ya", "kargil", "http://t.co/pQ0UoEun1K"], "ner_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PERSON", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": 34, "tokens": ["Simply", "Beautiful", "!!!", "kantilo", "Mahanadi", "#topview", "#mahanadi", "#river", "#trees", "#sky", "#beautifulview", "https://t.co/Uhk5quMz4L"], "ner_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": 35, "tokens": ["Aise", "lag", "rha", "hai", "sabne", "setting", "ki", "hui", "hai", "ek", "ball", "to", "khelne", "do", "meri", "batting", "nhi", "aayi", "...", "bhenchod", "!!!", "#IndvsPak"], "ner_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": 36, "tokens": ["Param", "Pujye", "sant", "Shiri", "Ashsram", "g", "bapu", "ke", "swasthye", "Yash", "kirti", "hetu", ",", "mahashivratri", "ke", "avsar", "per", "Ludhiana", "me", ".", "sadhkon", "http://t.co/Trakdy1njz"], "ner_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "B-PERSON", "I-PERSON", "I-PERSON", "I-PERSON", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PLACE", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": 37, "tokens": ["Patna", "Mahashivratri", "-", "17", "Feb", "2015", "(", "MahaShivratri", ")", "HAR", "HAR", "MAHADEV", "Today", "returned", "Patna", "from", "...", "http://t.co/vPxTZR3uvK"], "ner_tags": ["B-PLACE", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PERSON", "O", "O", "B-PLACE", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": 38, "tokens": ["RT", "@sandhiriansgrp", ":", "Remember", "Guys", "kalpana", "chawala", "first", "Indian", "women", "astronaut", "who", "visit", "space", "1st", "Feb", "belongs", "to", "her", "@Varsharoy5", "https", ":/"], "ner_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PERSON", "I-PERSON", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": 39, "tokens": ["@eye_nakshiran", "abhi", "tak", "tum", "think", "he", "kar", "rahi", "ho", "naira", "pe", "he", "hogi"], "ner_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": 40, "tokens": ["RT", "@GoutamRishi", ":", "@akshaysonal", "@arvindkejriwal", "@madhukishwar", "@msisodia", "@irsad555", "ya", "Kishwar", "maam", "is", "propagating", "@zeenews"], "ner_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PERSON", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": 41, "tokens": ["Aaaattt", "..", "Mass", "ka", "BAAP", "https://t.co/POYlUVtn6t"], "ner_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": 42, "tokens": ["RT", "@narendramodi", ":", "I", "salute", "Sadanandan", "Master", "&", "many", "others", "like", "him", "who", "withstood", "Communist", "violence", "&", "continued", "to", "serve", "people", ".", "https://t"], "ner_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PERSON", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": 43, "tokens": ["PMOIndia", "#UHF", "RT", "RailMinIndia", ":", "Surveillance", "cameras", "on", "select", "mainline", "and", "ladies", "compartments", "#RailBudget2015", "Cat", "http://t.co/e6N6TyWi5n"], "ner_tags": ["B-ORGANISATION", "O", "O", "B-ORGANISATION", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": 44, "tokens": ["RT", "@diyainsan", ":", "Milliins", "of", "people", "had", "enjiyed", "#PiousBhandara", "&", "looted", "the", "divine", ",", "spiritual", "blessings", "https://t.co/n9G4Bdq77V"], "ner_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": 45, "tokens": ["Koi", "faryaad", "tere", "dil", "mein", "dabi", "ho", "jese", "Tu", "ne", "ankhon", "se", "koi", "baat", "kahi", "ho", "jese"], "ner_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": 46, "tokens": ["Modi's", "degree", "is", "not", "fake", ".........", "Does", "it", "matter", "???", "Ask", "Kanhaiya", "Kumar", "....,", "#KejriwalSaySorry"], "ner_tags": ["B-PERSON", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PERSON", "I-PERSON", "O", "O"]}
{"id": 47, "tokens": ["Happy", "#Mahashivratri", "to", "everyone", ".", "Jai", "Mahadev", ",", "Jai", "Bholeshankar", ",", "Jai", "ho", "Mahakaal", "ki", "."], "ner_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PERSON", "O", "O", "B-PERSON", "O", "O", "O", "B-PERSON", "O", "O"]}
{"id": 48, "tokens": ["#YoSoniaSoPoor", "that", "soon", "Rahul", "Gandhi", "would", "empower", "her", ".", "#IfModiBecomesPM", "#Modi"], "ner_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "B-PERSON", "I-PERSON", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": 49, "tokens": ["@FalguniRanpise", "haan", "but", "raman", "is", "drunk"], "ner_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "B-PERSON", "O", "O"]}
{"id": 50, "tokens": ["RT", "@ashu3page", ":", "So", "well", "managed", "this", "time", "@rvmoorthyhindu", ":", "second", "day", "of", "janta", "darbar", "by", "Delhi", "CM", "Arvind", "Kejriwal", "at", "kaushambi", ".", "http://t.co/2"], "ner_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PLACE", "O", "B-PERSON", "I-PERSON", "O", "B-PLACE", "O", "O"]}
{"id": 51, "tokens": ["RT", "@1ost__", ":", "Bhout", "Pareshan", "Hun", "Sab", "Ky", "Parchy", "ho", "rahy", "Aur", "Mujh", "Py", "Parchy"], "ner_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": 52, "tokens": ["Happy", "Mahashivratri", "Jai", "Bhole", "Nath", "Har", "Har", "Mahadev", "DS", "*", "http://t.co/ssTDoxRQ4h"], "ner_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "B-PERSON", "I-PERSON", "O", "O", "B-PERSON", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": 53, "tokens": ["RT", "@Kumar_Ke5hav", ":", "Dekh", "rahi", "hai", "sari", "duniya", "#ModiScaredOfSonia", "!"], "ner_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": 54, "tokens": ["RT", "@TheRajKundra", ":", "Australia", "walon", "ko", "pata", "nahin", "hai", ",", "kitna", "bhi", "target", "ho", ",", "hum", "India", "wale", "March", "mahine", "mein", "pura", "kar", "hi", "dete", "hain", "..."], "ner_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "B-PLACE", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PLACE", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": 55, "tokens": ["Tweet", "No", ":", "4000", "#", "#MahaShivratri", "Om", "Namashivaya", "#Tanjore", "#Lord", "Shiva", "http://t.co/LJQRu2jXkS"], "ner_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PERSON", "O"]}
{"id": 56, "tokens": ["#LandAcquisitionBill", "is", "good", "for", "???", "AAM", "Adami", "Ya", "Special", "AAdami", "#LandAcquisitionBill", "Zameen", "Wapsi", "Andolan", "#WhereIsRahul"], "ner_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": 57, "tokens": ["@join2manish", "Reminds", "me", "of", "'", "Rang", "de", "tu", "mohe", "gerua", ":-)", "'"], "ner_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": 58, "tokens": ["#ZalmiRocks", "yahan", "ek", "wicket", "ki", "zarorat", "hy"], "ner_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": 60, "tokens": ["RT", "@nalinisinghtv", ":", "Renowned", "Shri", "Pashupati", "Nath", "Temple", "complex", "in", "Kathmandu", "has", "sufferred", "no", "damage", ",", "is", "safe", ",", "acc", "to", "reports", "."], "ner_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PLACE", "I-PLACE", "I-PLACE", "I-PLACE", "O", "O", "B-PLACE", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": 61, "tokens": ["RT", "@EconomicTimes", ":", "Rail", "Minister", "Suresh", "Prabhu", "and", "MoS", "Manoj", "Sinha", "with", "#RailBudget2015", "suitcases", "http://t.co/8BH8qiUuee"], "ner_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PERSON", "I-PERSON", "O", "O", "B-PERSON", "I-PERSON", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": 62, "tokens": ["#IndvsSA", "A", ".", "B", ".", "De", "villiers", "will", "take", "revenge", "from", "dhawan", ".", "India", "waalo", ",", "#patakhe", "footenge", "?"], "ner_tags": ["O", "B-PERSON", "I-PERSON", "I-PERSON", "I-PERSON", "I-PERSON", "I-PERSON", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PERSON", "O", "B-PLACE", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": 63, "tokens": ["@Gurmeetramrahim", "#MSGsalutes", "We", "also", "salute", "papa", "ji"], "ner_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": 64, "tokens": ["RT", "@neeraj_raturi", ":", "@aaprohit", "@ArvindKejriwal", "sir", "ji", "apke", "pass", "kuch", "kam", "nahi", "kya", ",", "ap", "ne", "vi", "vat", "tax", "kun", "badhaya", "hai", "usko", "vi", "waps", "karo", "......."], "ner_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": 65, "tokens": ["Delhi", "Cantt", ",", "Greater", "Kailash", ",", "Jangpura", ",", "malvia", "nagar", ",", "patparganj", ",", "New", "Delhi", "#DilliAAPki", "#DelhiDecides"], "ner_tags": ["B-PLACE", "I-PLACE", "O", "B-PLACE", "I-PLACE", "O", "B-PLACE", "O", "B-PLACE", "I-PLACE", "O", "B-PLACE", "O", "B-PLACE", "I-PLACE", "O", "O"]}
{"id": 66, "tokens": ["RT", "@rameshsrivats", ":", "Now", ",", "waiting", "for", "Abhijeet", "to", "blame", "those", "dumb", "blackbucks", "for", "hanging", "around", "in", "the", "path", "of", "a", "bullet", "."], "ner_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PERSON", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": 67, "tokens": ["@pacificleo", "Crafts", "Museum", ".", "Bhairon", "road", ".", "Delhi", "."], "ner_tags": ["O", "B-PLACE", "I-PLACE", "O", "B-PLACE", "I-PLACE", "O", "B-PLACE", "O"]}
{"id": 68, "tokens": ["@prek_rk", "@sankalparkapoor", "ok", "but", "famous", "toh", "main", "aur", "katrina", "hi", "zyada", "honge"], "ner_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PERSON", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": 69, "tokens": ["@justbeauty18", "Abi", "koi", "kasaar", "baqi", "hy", "?", ":D"], "ner_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": 70, "tokens": ["@arpitduryodhan", "Har", "Har", "Mahadev", ":)", "Happy", "Mahashivratri", ":)", "Om", "Namah", "Siva", ":)", "http://t.co/BCFIQr3mGZ"], "ner_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "B-PERSON", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PERSON", "O", "O"]}
{"id": 71, "tokens": ["Red-faced", "Kavita", "Krishnan", "!", "#MahaShivratri", "#BlockBusterMSG", "#RiseAboveRacism", "#", "Lord", "Shiva"], "ner_tags": ["O", "B-PERSON", "I-PERSON", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PERSON"]}
{"id": 72, "tokens": ["RT", "chiraginsan77", ":", "RT", "giftyinsan", ":", "Thank", "you", "so", "much", "papa", "kl", "apne", "bahut", "maza", "thank", "you", "thank", "you", "thank", "you", "#MustWatchMSG", "#BlockBusterMSG"], "ner_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": 73, "tokens": ["RT", "@OfficeOfRG", ":", "Will", "be", "in", "Chhattisgarh", "tomorrow", "14th", "March", ",", "to", "participate", "in", "the", "Girodhpuri", "Mela", "and", "visit", "the", "Guru", "Gaddi", "Temple"], "ner_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PLACE", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PLACE", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PLACE", "I-PLACE", "I-PLACE"]}
{"id": 74, "tokens": ["Happy", "Mahashivratri", "to", "all", ".", "Har", "Har", "Mahadev", ".", "Jai", "Shiv", "Shankar", ".", "Om", "Namah", "Shivay", ".", "He", "is", "the", "devo", "ke", "dev", "Mahadev", ".", "#MahaShivratri"], "ner_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PERSON", "O", "O", "B-PERSON", "I-PERSON", "O", "O", "O", "B-PERSON", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PERSON", "O", "O"]}
{"id": 75, "tokens": ["Journo", ":", "How", "is", "#RailBudget2015", "?", "Harsha", "Bhogle", ":", "The", "two", "best", "Bangladesh", "batsmen", "are", "Mushfiqur", "Rahim", "and", "Shakib", "al", "Hasan", "."], "ner_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PERSON", "I-PERSON", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PLACE", "O", "O", "B-PERSON", "I-PERSON", "O", "B-PERSON", "I-PERSON", "I-PERSON", "O"]}
{"id": 76, "tokens": ["RT", "@mvmeet", ":", "Modi", "forcefully", "taking", "away", "gas", "cylinder", "frm", "a", "Muslim", "woman", "&", "giving", "to", "a", "Hindu", ":", "-", "Kejriwal", "#CongTerrorInRajyaSabha", "https://t", "."], "ner_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "B-PERSON", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PERSON", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": 77, "tokens": ["RT", "@ChouhanShivraj", ":", "'", "Parv", "Snan", "'", "this", "morning", "at", "the", "holy", "river", "Kshipra", "in", "Ujjain", ".", "Pilgrims", "'", "take", "holy", "dip", "with", "great", "devotion", ".", "https://t.co"], "ner_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PLACE", "O", "B-PLACE", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": 78, "tokens": ["@karachikhatmal", "@Nicks103", "saha", "b", "akmal", "bretheraan", "hai", ".", "Dil", "kre", "toh", "acha", "khel", "liya", "varna", "sab", "ko", "saath", "lekar", "doobta", "hai"], "ner_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": 79, "tokens": ["frastu", "singh", "-", "the", "Biggest", "Supporter", "of", "Rahul", "Gandhi", "reacting", "on", "Modi", "becoming", "BJP", "prime-ministerial", "candidate", "http://t.co/H65r70BqXJ"], "ner_tags": ["B-PERSON", "I-PERSON", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PERSON", "I-PERSON", "O", "O", "B-PERSON", "O", "B-ORGANISATION", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": 80, "tokens": ["Muharam", "celebrations", "in", "Indian", "hyderabad", "#IndvsPak", "#", "#IndWins", "#WorldCup", "#FuckYouPak"], "ner_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PLACE", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": 81, "tokens": ["RT", "@sureshnakhua", ":", "#MahaShivRatri", "108", "Names", "of", "Lord", "Shiva", "25", ".", "-", "Kamari", "-", "Enemy", "of", "Kamadeva", "#"], "ner_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PERSON", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PERSON", "O"]}
{"id": 82, "tokens": ["RT", "@hushar_mulga", ":", "Bhai", "Ab", "koe", "rahul", "Gandhi", "k", "bare", "me", "mat", "puchna", "...", "#RahulOnLeave", "Congress", ":", "http://t.co/isAIm9itAm"], "ner_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PERSON", "I-PERSON", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORGANISATION", "O", "O"]}
{"id": 83, "tokens": ["Happy", "Mahashivratri", "folks", ":)", "..", "Har", "Har", "Bole", "..", "Om", "Namah", "Shivay"], "ner_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": 84, "tokens": ["No", "change", "in", "team", "hum", "to", "batting", "hi", "karege", "...", "Are", "ye", "anushka", "kidhar", "hai", "..", "#IndvsSA"], "ner_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PERSON", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": 85, "tokens": ["RT", "@Aum_Shakti", ":", "Bahut", "Krantikari", ";", "Pakki", "#Aaptard", "@ArvindKejriwal", "@ReporterVikrant", "https://t.co/AbXVZdDDNt", "hereIsRahul"], "ner_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": 86, "tokens": ["Nursing", "student", "gangraped", "by", "3", "persons", "in", "Kerala", "#WomenInIndia", "#disgusting", "#DalitRights", "https://t.co/lHn238veau", "https://t.co/3uyYI0uYHn"], "ner_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PLACE", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": 87, "tokens": ["#IndvsPak", "hahaha", "...", "maza", "a", "gya", "...", "back", "to", "back", "wicket", "...", "yoyo"], "ner_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": 88, "tokens": ["@saurabhraajjain", "MahaShivRatri", "pe", "Mahadev", "ke", "sbse", "priya", "bhakt", "aur", "aradhya", "#Narayan", "ki", "yad", "aa", "hi", "rhi", "thi", ".", "Happy", "ShivRatri", "to", "u", "&", "ur", "family", ":)"], "ner_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "B-PERSON", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": 89, "tokens": ["RT", "@RealHistoryPic", ":", "Priyanka", "Gandhi", "displaying", "tricks", "of", "martial", "arts", "in", "order", "to", "counter", "the", "Eve", "teasers", "of", "Gujarat", ".", "(", "2014", ")", "https://t.co/b"], "ner_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "B-PERSON", "I-PERSON", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PLACE", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": 90, "tokens": ["Om", "sam", "shaneshcharaaye", "namah", "!!!"], "ner_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": 91, "tokens": ["#IndvsSA", "I", "have", "told", "today", "morning", "killed", "hum", "mauke", "pe", "chuka", "marenge", "......"], "ner_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": 92, "tokens": ["@Womaniya", "Aaj", "phir", "dil", "ne", "ek", "tamanna", "ki", "...", "aaj", "phir", "dil", "ko", "humne", "samjhaya", "#JagjitSingh", "#Lyrics", "#JavedAkhtar"], "ner_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": 94, "tokens": ["Muh", "m", "rajnigandha", "Dimag", "m", "surur", "#RajnigandhaSixWordsStory", "https://t.co/naR0ZJ3eqc"], "ner_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": 95, "tokens": ["Ratnai", "Kalpit", "Masanam", "|", "Hey", "Shiva", "|", "Dr.", "Soma", "Ghosh", ":", "http://t.co/bQGmroG9eU", "#MahaShivratri"], "ner_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PERSON", "O", "O", "B-PERSON", "I-PERSON", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": 96, "tokens": ["That", "sema", "song", "by", "@thisisysr", "!", "Kadhal", "Vandhale", "!", "@iam_str", "#Vallavan"], "ner_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": 97, "tokens": ["RT", "@NaIna0806", ":", "While", "Rahul", "was", "fooling", "around", "with", "rehearsed", "speeches", "it", "was", "#SmritiIrani", "who", "was", "at", "#Amethi", "solving", "real", "issues", ".", "https://"], "ner_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PERSON", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": 98, "tokens": ["Jta", "se", "nikle", "gangadhar", "Haatho", "me", "liye", "Damru", "Shrishti", "k", "jo", "hain", "palanhar", "Aaj", "hai", "Shiv", "ji", "ka", "tyohaar", "Happy", "Mahashivratri", "#Akki"], "ner_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "B-PERSON", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PERSON", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PERSON", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": 99, "tokens": ["Mera", "dil", "kal", "school", "jany", "ko", "bilkul", "ni", "kr", "ra", "bs", "dil", "kr", "ra", "ha", "k", "janamaz", "pr", "beth", "kr", "#pak", "k", "liye", "dua", "krn", "..", "allah", "g", "plz", "help", "..", "#pakvsind", "#indvspak"], "ner_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": 100, "tokens": ["@SemperFiUnited", "i", "understand", "only", "punjabi", "..", "Bund", "marva", "pancho", "!"], "ner_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": 101, "tokens": ["@AmitShahOffice", "@narendramodi", "@Bihar_BJP", "pls", "don't", "vote", "in", "side", "of", "#Manjhi", "bahut", "wrong", "msg", "jata", "hai", "party", "k", "baare", "me", "public", "me", ",", "Plz", "don't"], "ner_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": 102, "tokens": ["@Obnoxious_Ravan", "Dil", "tod", "diya", "janeman", "...", "ab", "ni", "aaunga", "mai", "wapis", "twitter", "pe", ":\\", "@gillraman705", "@confusedbf_"], "ner_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORGANISATION", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": 103, "tokens": ["@abhisar_sharma", ":", "CHIRKUT", "Patrakar", "Mahoday", "...", "HYD", "par", "Hi", "dhyan", "Lagao", "..,", "wahan", "TRP", "nikalti", "hai", "."], "ner_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "B-PERSON", "I-PERSON", "O", "B-PLACE", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": 104, "tokens": ["@MahaMahadev", "Aap", "bhi", "Pahuncho", "na", "Aandolan", "me", "..", "Akele", "inn", "hi", "logo", "ki", "thekedari", "hai", "kya", "?", "@DrKumarVishwas", "@MyCMKejariwal", "#LandAcquisitionBill"], "ner_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": 105, "tokens": ["@cynic_wall", "bipasha", "horror", "films", "zyada", "karti", "h", ".", "lovely", "ni", ":p"], "ner_tags": ["O", "B-PERSON", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": 106, "tokens": ["@Rekhta", "hahahhahaahaha", "great", "sher", "yaar", "!!", "bahoot", "khoob", "!!!"], "ner_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": 107, "tokens": ["RT", "@rishibagree", ":", "Contrast", "this", "with", "BJP", "Atal", "Bihari", "Vajpayee's", "Lok", "Sabha", "speech", "when", "they", "were", "short", "of", "nos", ".", "http://t.co/ezANVnE0R3", "#AAP"], "ner_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORGANISATION", "B-PERSON", "I-PERSON", "I-PERSON", "B-ORGANISATION", "I-ORGANISATION", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": 108, "tokens": ["#ModiSlapsChina", "Dont", "go", "overboard", "with", "hashtag", "business", ",", "foreign", "policy", "is", "not", "about", "hashtags", "."], "ner_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": 109, "tokens": ["Gujarat", "was", "labelled", "as", "one", "of", "the", "safest", "states", "of", "India", "and", "suddenly", "Sardar", "Patel", "ka", "naam", "le", "ke", "bus", "jalao", ",...", "http://t.co/7wzssKkGds"], "ner_tags": ["B-PLACE", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PLACE", "O", "O", "B-PERSON", "I-PERSON", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": 110, "tokens": ["RT", "@giniromet", ":", "If", "a", "woman", "is", "super", "successful", "(", "Kangana", "Ranaut", ")", "she", "is", "called", "psychopath", "If", "a", "man", "is", "super", "successful", "(", "Modi", ")", "he", "is", "also", "cal"], "ner_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PERSON", "I-PERSON", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PERSON", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": 111, "tokens": ["Sooraj", "Pancholi", "rocks", "the", "Lonely", "Planet", "Magazine", "India", "Awards", ":", "All", "roads", "of", "tinsel", "town", "lead", "to", "the", "Lonely", "Pl", "...", "https://t.co/RK3yFhYSg4"], "ner_tags": ["B-PERSON", "I-PERSON", "O", "O", "B-ORGANISATION", "I-ORGANISATION", "I-ORGANISATION", "B-PLACE", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": 112, "tokens": ["\"", "Trending", "India", ":", "03:51", "PM", "IST", "\"", "1", ".", "#IPLAuction", "2", ".", "#MustWatchMSG", "3", ".", "#WIvIRE", "4", ".", "#AwardWinningExcuses", "5", ".", "Yograj", "Singh", "6", ".", "Ireland"], "ner_tags": ["O", "O", "B-PLACE", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PERSON", "I-PERSON", "O", "O", "B-PLACE"]}
{"id": 113, "tokens": ["@JoinAAP", "@prena_", "baap", "re", "baap", "free", "khor", "ho", "saare", "Ke", "saare", "#AAPtards", ".", "Mehnat", "se", "kuch", "mat", "karna"], "ner_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": 114, "tokens": ["Na", "Jane", "kb", "Koi", "Tara", "Toot", "Jae", ";", "Na", "Jane", "Kb", "Koi", "Aansu", "Aankh", "Se", "Chhoot", "Jaye", ";", "Kuch", "Pal", "Hamare", "Sath", "Bhi", "Has", "Lo", ";", "Na", "Jane", "Kb", "Tumhare", "Daant", "Toot", "Jae", "!"], "ner_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": 115, "tokens": ["@narendramodi", "ji", ",", "Good", "morning", "!", "MahaShivratri", "KI", "badhai", "ho", ".", "http://t.co/hLuNUz5btQ"], "ner_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": 116, "tokens": ["RT", "@EconomicTimes", ":", "How", "Prabhu's", "#RailBudget2015", "has", "#Modi's", "mantras", "http://t.co/EJad1fdDci", "|", "Full", "Coverage", "http://t.co/7xeEi8eaOv", "http://t", "."], "ner_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PERSON", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": 117, "tokens": ["Andhra", "Pradesh", "becomes", "first", "state", "to", "achieve", "inter-linking", "of", "rivers", ":", "CM", "N", "Chandrababu", "Naidu", "@EconomicTimes", "https://t.co/AmsEDxm1q6"], "ner_tags": ["B-PLACE", "I-PLACE", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PERSON", "I-PERSON", "I-PERSON", "O", "O"]}
{"id": 118, "tokens": ["@Gurmeetramrahim", "#MSGsocialWelfare", "hey", "malik", "din", "bhar", "mai", "mujhse", "aisa", "koi", "karam", "na", "ho", "jo", "apki", "najar", "mai", "gunah", "ho", "@@@"], "ner_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": 119, "tokens": ["J&K", ":", "NC", "veteran", "Sheikh", "Nazir", "dies", "#RSSQuestionsTeresa", "#WhereIsRahul", "#RahulOnLeave", "#MSGRevolution", "#WIvZIM", "http://t.co/nIAhdjpzbI"], "ner_tags": ["B-PLACE", "O", "O", "O", "B-PERSON", "I-PERSON", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": 120, "tokens": ["RT", "@UbcanilGupta", ":", "Arvind", "Kejriwal", "should", "tender", "public", "apology", "for", "remarks", "on", "PM", "Narendra", "Modi's", "degrees", ":", "BJP", "https://t.co/N7SIrV0SF0"], "ner_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "B-PERSON", "I-PERSON", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PERSON", "I-PERSON", "O", "O", "B-ORGANISATION", "O"]}
{"id": 121, "tokens": ["Nayi", "chahte", ",", "nayi", "umange", "..", "Mann", "mein", "h", "ek", "khuwab", "naya", "sa", "Nayi", "hai", "saal", ",", "naya", "hai", "din", "Rakho", "andaaz", "ese", "jine", "ka", "...", "https://t.co/02JCxyIH95"], "ner_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": 122, "tokens": ["RT", "@MIB_India", ":", "Nine", "major", "thrust", "areas", "in", "#RailBudget2015", "presented", "by", "Shri", "@sureshpprabhu", "#", "http://t.co/ePfEN6Cf1l"], "ner_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": 123, "tokens": ["RT", "@sharma11ashish1", ":", "SC", "rejects", "the", "petition", "of", "the", "9", "rebel", "Cong", "MLAs", ".", "The", "MLAs", "cant", "vote", "in", "tomorrow's", "floor", "test", "in", "Uttarakhand", ".", "@shailesh"], "ner_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "B-ORGANISATION", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORGANISATION", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PLACE", "O", "O"]}
{"id": 124, "tokens": ["@indiantweeter", "uma", "bharti", "ka", ":)", ":p"], "ner_tags": ["O", "B-PERSON", "I-PERSON", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": 125, "tokens": ["@sachin_rt", "&", "Suresh", "Prabhu", ",", "railway", "minister", "belong", "to", "same", "school", ",", "Shardashram", "vidya", "mandir", "...", "#RailBudget2015"], "ner_tags": ["O", "O", "B-PERSON", "I-PERSON", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORGANISATION", "I-ORGANISATION", "I-ORGANISATION", "O", "O"]}
{"id": 126, "tokens": ["Happy", "MahaShivratri", "...", ":", ":", "Deh", "Shiva", "eh", "bar", "mohe-i-hai", "shubh", "karman", "the", "kabhu", "na", "taroo", "Na", "daroo", "ar", "siyoo", "...", "http://t.co/3PnISEtDxe"], "ner_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PERSON", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": 127, "tokens": ["RT", "@ImLeslieChow", ":", "Girlfriend", "?", "Is", "that", "a", "rare", "Pokemon", "?"], "ner_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": 128, "tokens": ["RT", "@arunvipra", ":", "Finally", "kejriwal", "launches", "free", "wifi", "....", "and", "Laaloo", "receives", "signals", "https://t.co/Fg5qReiwev"], "ner_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PERSON", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PERSON", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": 129, "tokens": ["RT", "@galat_fehmi", ":", "Nahaya", "karo", ",", "bohot", "soap", "hai", "."], "ner_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": 130, "tokens": ["#MahaShivratri", "\"", "@IndiaHistorypic", ":", "Mallikarjuna", "Swamy", "Temple", ",", "Srisailam", "in", "Andhra", "Pradesh", ",", "one", "of", "the", "12", "Jyotirlingas", "http://t.co/5gH2KPZ5h3", "\""], "ner_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PLACE", "I-PLACE", "I-PLACE", "O", "B-PLACE", "O", "B-PLACE", "I-PLACE", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": 131, "tokens": ["@Dev__Raj", "pl", "change", "ur", "DP2", "Low", "IQ", "Low", "EQ", "BHAKT", "DALAL", "of", "Pradhan", "Dalal", "of", "zAdani", "zAmbani", "SwissAcc", "@narendramodi", "Congress", "@BJP4India", "BhaiBhai"], "ner_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PERSON", "B-PERSON", "O", "O", "B-ORGANISATION", "O", "O"]}
{"id": 132, "tokens": ["Aaj", "Phir", "Harayenge", "Kyunki", "Aadat", "Hai", ".", "#IndvsPak"], "ner_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": 134, "tokens": ["@snehal_gandhi", "Delhi", "walon", "ko", "gussa", "aa", "hi", "jaata", "hai", "Pak", "ke", "saamne", ".", "Remember", "Gauti", "!", "Shikhar", "&", "Kohli", "proving", "it", "again", ".", "#IndvsPak", "#CWC15"], "ner_tags": ["O", "B-PLACE", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PLACE", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PERSON", "O", "B-PERSON", "O", "B-PERSON", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": 135, "tokens": ["@Gurmeetramrahim", "#PiousBhandara", "guru", "ji", "initiated", "5", "more", "humanitarian", "works", "on", "the", "auspicious", "day", "of", "foundation", "day"], "ner_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": 136, "tokens": ["@MahnooriAhmed", "ya", "alllah", "yeh", "kya", "kiya", "hahahah"], "ner_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": 137, "tokens": ["Sri", "Krishna", "Ultimate", "Symbol", "of", "Love", ".", "Happy", "Valentine", "Day", "....", "http://t.co/zCvoxUT0"], "ner_tags": ["O", "B-PERSON", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": 138, "tokens": ["Silent", "Message", "for", "all", "of", "you", "guys", ",,,,,,,,,", "Hahhahaha", "AAP", "MLA", "Akhilesh", "Tripathi", "#Intolerance", "@AAPMagic", "@aapkipreeti", "https://t.co/hivfuI3I2n"], "ner_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORGANISATION", "O", "B-PERSON", "I-PERSON", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": 139, "tokens": ["@TheMusicLegends", "for", "Kishoreda", "Lataji", "and", "BigB", "&", "@Zeenat_Amaan", "fans", "https://t.co/EPAaIg5fJu"], "ner_tags": ["O", "O", "B-PERSON", "B-PERSON", "O", "B-PERSON", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": 141, "tokens": ["RT", "@BeingSalmanKhan", ":", "Happy", "Birthday", "to", "my", "Sultani", "Arfa", "#SultanKiJaan", "@SultanTheMovie", "@AnushkaSharma", ".", "https://t.co/bII4Ij71bg"], "ner_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PERSON", "I-PERSON", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": 142, "tokens": ["#RailBudget2015", "@RailMinIndia", "hopefully", "this", "time", "will", "be", "discuss", "about", "Silchar", ",", "lumding", "broad", "gauge", "line"], "ner_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PLACE", "O", "B-PLACE", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": 143, "tokens": ["RT", "@IndiaBTL", ":", "Sonia", "is", "not", "Indira", ",", "&", "@narendramodi", "is", "no", "Morarji", "to", "arrest", "her", "till", "there's", "irrefutable", "proof", "Sonia's", "foster", "son", "Kejri", "is", "o"], "ner_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "B-PERSON", "O", "O", "B-PERSON", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PERSON", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PERSON", "O", "O", "B-PERSON", "O", "O"]}
{"id": 144, "tokens": ["Keralites", "should", "actually", "be", "scared", "of", "Modi's", "promise", "to", "turn", "Kerala", "into", "another", "Gujarat", ",,", "=))", ",,", "https://t.co/wDTaPN3keA"], "ner_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PERSON", "O", "O", "O", "B-PLACE", "O", "O", "B-PLACE", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": 145, "tokens": ["@ajaydevgn", "Sir", "Ji", "Is", "MahashivRatri", "k", "Parv", "par", "#SHIVAAY", "Movie", "k", "Baare", "Me", "Kuch", "Bataye"], "ner_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": 147, "tokens": ["RT", "@cricketnext", ":", "Just", "in", ":", "Cricketer", "Ravindra", "Jadeja's", "marriage", "runs", "into", "controversy", "after", "gunfire", "shots", "during", "marriage", "procession"], "ner_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PERSON", "I-PERSON", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": 148, "tokens": ["Chumma", "chahye", ".", "I", "promise", "mai", "wapis", "kardunga", "."], "ner_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": 149, "tokens": ["RT", "@SomeGoanGuy", ":", "These", "Gujarat", "Jersey", "colours", "have", "been", "inspired", "by", "Jethalal", "Gada", "for", "sure", "#KXIPvGL"], "ner_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PLACE", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PERSON", "I-PERSON", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": 150, "tokens": ["...", "abhi", "aayega", "rukiye", "\"", "@mehrishisumati", ":", "Once", "upon", "a", "time", "there", "was", "a", "hashtag", "#RailBudget2015", "\""], "ner_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": 151, "tokens": ["Rahul", "Gandhi", "is", "behaving", "like", "an", "Engineering", "student", ".", "Koi", "kaam", "na", "dhaam", ",", "phir", "bhi", "chutti", "chahiye", ".", "#RahulOnLeave"], "ner_tags": ["B-PERSON", "I-PERSON", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": 152, "tokens": ["Spectacular", "Site", "to", "behold", ".", "Vansda", "Raj", "Rajeshvar", "Mahadev", "Mandir", "in", "Gujarat", ".", "#harharmahadev", "#MahaShivratri", "http://t.co/sOxhGVcNDj"], "ner_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PLACE", "I-PLACE", "I-PLACE", "I-PLACE", "I-PLACE", "O", "B-PLACE", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": 153, "tokens": ["RT", "@LOLendraSingh", ":", "Pradhanmantri", "Ujjwala", "Yojna", "in", "a", "nutshell", ".", "https://t.co/d0RltF3PnI"], "ner_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": 154, "tokens": ["RT", "@NtvteluguHD", ":", "Nandamuri", "Balakrishna", "Super", "Comedy", "Speech", "@", "Savitri", "Movie", "Audio", "Launch", ".", "https://t.co/JNjvrGzOzT"], "ner_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "B-PERSON", "I-PERSON", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": 155, "tokens": ["Om", "Namah", "Shivaya", "Dhun", "|", "Dhyan", "Sankirtan", "::", "http://t.co/qsX0KiHuaD", "http://t.co/VZuM3DURKj", "via", "@sharethis", "#MahaShivratri", "#", "Lord", "Shiva"], "ner_tags": ["O", "O", "B-PERSON", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PERSON"]}
{"id": 156, "tokens": ["MerryXmas", "From", "TeamShivaay", "santa", "is", "waiting", "waiting", "waiting"], "ner_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": 157, "tokens": ["Jai", "bhole", "baba", "Happy", "mahashivratri", "@akshaykumar", "sir", ",", "@mrsfunnybones", "mam", "&", "all", "akkians", "."], "ner_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": 158, "tokens": ["#IndvsPak", "koi", "ye", "to", "btao", "ye", "hmare", "player", "face", "p", "kch", "lga", "k", "ae", "h", "ya", "pak", "s", "match", "ki", "khushi", "m", "special", "facial", "?", ":-P"], "ner_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PLACE", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": 159, "tokens": ["Aaj", "naashta", "Lahore", "mein", ",", "lunch", "Karachi", "aur", "dinner", "Islamabad", "mein", ".", "#IndvsPak"], "ner_tags": ["O", "O", "B-PLACE", "O", "O", "O", "B-PLACE", "O", "O", "B-PLACE", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": 160, "tokens": ["@AltruisticPooja", "baat", "mey", "duum", "to", "hy", "bus", "abki", "mahashivratri", "pey", "obama", "ji", "ko", "bula", "he", "liya", "jaye", "kashi", "ganga", "isnan", "k", "liye", "kaam", "ban", "jayega"], "ner_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PERSON", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": 161, "tokens": ["Madhuri", "Dixit", "at", "the", "screening", "of", "Shahrukh", "Khan's", "FAN", "movie", ".", "See", "video", "at", ":", "https://t.co/uYmqNjNmG0", "#madhuridixit", "#shahrukhkhan", "#fan"], "ner_tags": ["B-PERSON", "I-PERSON", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PERSON", "I-PERSON", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": 162, "tokens": ["Bam", "Bam", "Bam", "Om", "Namah", "Shivaya", "(", ")-Sankirtan", "and", "Dhyan", "http://t.co/RrvstKP58y", "#bapuji", "#Mahashivratri"], "ner_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": 163, "tokens": ["Pakistan", ":", "Kashmir", "rehnedo", "kohli", "dedo", "Indian", ":", "Abeeeee", "bhaaag", "hahahaha", "#IndvsPak", "#MaukaMauka"], "ner_tags": ["B-PLACE", "O", "B-PLACE", "O", "B-PERSON", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": 164, "tokens": ["Mohe", "Rang", "dho", "laal", "#BajiraoMastani", "@deepikapadukone", "charming", "song", "!!"], "ner_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": 165, "tokens": ["RT", "@tyagi40", ":", "@ITwingDSS", "@Gurmeetramrahim", "#MSGHonorToHumanity", "mera", "satguru", "bichado", "huo", "ko", "milwata", "h", "msg"], "ner_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PERSON", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": 166, "tokens": ["Congress", "Rail", "Budget", "Ko", "Gali", "De", "Raha", "Hai", "Jaise", "Unho", "Ne", "To", "Etne", "Salo", "Mein", "Indian", "Railway", "Ko", "China", "Railway", "Ke", "Jaisa", "Banaya", "Ho", "#RailBudget2015"], "ner_tags": ["B-ORGANISATION", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORGANISATION", "I-ORGANISATION", "O", "B-ORGANISATION", "I-ORGANISATION", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": 167, "tokens": ["#WhereIsRahul", "is", "trending", "No", "1", "on", "twitter", "worldwide", ".", "Common", "Rahul", "ab", "toh", "aa", "zao", ".", "Tumhe", "191", "mulko", "ke", "log", "dhoondh", "rahe", "hain"], "ner_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORGANISATION", "O", "O", "O", "B-PERSON", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": 168, "tokens": ["Roshan", "Akthar", "on", "eToro", "OpenBook", "https://t.co/btdTxu3qSp"], "ner_tags": ["B-PERSON", "I-PERSON", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": 169, "tokens": ["RT", "@INCIndia", ":", "Shri", "Modi", "in", "a", "tweet", "on", "31.3.2014", "said", ",", "\"", "Italian", "marines", "mercilessly", "killed", "our", "fishermen", ".", "If", "Madam", "is", "so", "'", "patriotic", "'", "can", "she"], "ner_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PERSON", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": 170, "tokens": ["@Shreela22", "I", "believe", "him", "but", "I", "m", "unable", "to", "understand", "ki", "yaar", "wo", "soch", "kya", "rhe", "h", ":/"], "ner_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": 171, "tokens": ["There", "should", "be", "more", "budget", "for", "railway", "lines", ".", "Nahi", "toh", "Delhi", "NCR", "ki", "roads", "ki", "tarah", "ho", "jana", "hai", "haal", ".", "#RailBudget2015"], "ner_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PLACE", "I-PLACE", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": 172, "tokens": ["Maneka", "Ghandhi", "with", "her", "Dogi(1957", ")", "Image", "Courtesy-", "PETA", ".", "#MustWatchMSG", "#BlockBusterMSG"], "ner_tags": ["B-PERSON", "I-PERSON", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORGANISATION", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": 173, "tokens": ["RT", "@toi_pDasgupta", ":", "Music", "director", "Debajyoti", "Mishra", "has", "hurled", "plagiarism", "charges", "against", "a", "Bangladeshi", "film", "4", "copying", "4m", "his", "'", "Piya", "tora", "'", "so"], "ner_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PERSON", "I-PERSON", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PLACE", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": 174, "tokens": ["RT", "@ndtv", ":", "Nepalese", "ambassador", "stays", "put", "in", "Delhi", "despite", "reports", "of", "recall", "https://t.co/Zj56TzIhBe", "https://t.co/yEqckOCvLG"], "ner_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PERSON", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": 175, "tokens": ["RT", "@MIB_India", ":", "RT", "@RailMinIndia", ":", "5", "Drivers", "to", "execute", "strategy", "of", "MR", "sureshprabhu", "#RailBudget2015", "http://t.co/Hnk41ATUPv"], "ner_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PERSON", "I-PERSON", "O", "O"]}
{"id": 176, "tokens": ["RT", "@uzma_sarang", ":", "It", "was", "@imVkohli", "vs", "@GautamGambhir", "and", "our", "Gambhir", "won", "#AmiKKR", "And", "Yusuf", "Bhai", "whatta", "comeback", "#KKRvsRCB"], "ner_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PERSON", "O", "O", "O", "B-PERSON", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": 177, "tokens": ["\"", "Imran", "Tahir", "may", "run", "all", "the", "way", "to", "Srilanka", "while", "celebrating", "a", "wicket", "at", "Chepauk", ".", "#CSKvsDD", "\""], "ner_tags": ["O", "B-PERSON", "I-PERSON", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PLACE", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PLACE", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": 178, "tokens": ["#railbudget2015", "no", "incrse", "in", "pasengr", "fare", "67%more", "funds", "fr", "passenger", "ammenities", "@Zahenaseeb", "@ggiittiikkaa", "@laidback1954", "@DrGPradhan", "@ExSecular"], "ner_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": 179, "tokens": ["RT", "@SChotepur", ":", "When", "will", "PM", "Modi", "ask", "CBI", "to", "make", "a", "Raid", "on", "\"", "Lootere", "\"", "(Akali-Congress-BJP)of", "Punjab", "..??", "@AamAadmiParty", "@ipathak25"], "ner_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PERSON", "O", "B-ORGANISATION", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PLACE", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": 180, "tokens": ["Feelng", "hawa", "hawai", "aftr", "two", "packs", "of", "bhang", "...", "har", "har", "mahadev", "#mahashivratri"], "ner_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PERSON", "O"]}
{"id": 181, "tokens": ["My", "ExRoomie", "&", "whenever", "I", "chk", "him", "on", "phone", "now", ".", "I", "remember", "\"", "Raj", ",", "naam", "to", "suna", "hi", "hoga", "\"", "(", "Yes", "https://t.co/xsQZqk8xDk", "https://t.co/R0lTcnQXKd"], "ner_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PERSON", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": 182, "tokens": ["When", "I", "was", "1", "year", "old", "My", "parents", "took", "me", "to", "watch", "Sanam", "Bewafa", ",", "this", "was", "my", "first", "film", "in", "cinema", "hall", "(", "Kuch", "bhi", "...", "https://t.co/MVd1qcKwRp"], "ner_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": 183, "tokens": ["RT", "@LiteraryBadass", ":", "Arvind", "Kejriwal", "is", "like", "Vidya", "Balan", "in", "Kahaani", ".", "Only", "looks", "pregnant", ",", "never", "delivers", "."], "ner_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "B-PERSON", "I-PERSON", "O", "O", "B-PERSON", "I-PERSON", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": 184, "tokens": ["Zindagi", "Chinese", "film", "ki", "tarah", "ho", "gai", "hay", "dekh", "rahe", "hain", "but", "samjh", "nahi", "aa", "rahi"], "ner_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": 185, "tokens": ["RT", "@SirJadeja", ":", "Ab", "Australia", "Dekhegi", "India", "Ke", "Tevar", "Jab", "Unko", "Dhoyenge", "Anushka", "Ke", "Devar", ".", ";)", "RT", "if", "you're", "Waiting", "For", "#IndvsAus", "#AUSvIND", "#CW"], "ner_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PLACE", "O", "B-PLACE", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PERSON", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": 186, "tokens": ["'", "Saturday", "Night", "Live", "'", "Recap", ":", "Brie", "Larson", "Hosts", "a", "Show", "More", "Sweet", "Than", "Salty", "-", "https://t.co/lLHmul3Wux"], "ner_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PERSON", "I-PERSON", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": 187, "tokens": ["In", "Hindi", "-", "MahaShivratri", "ki", "dher", "saari", "subhkamnae", "!!!!", "In", "English", "-", "Happy", "MahaShivratri", "to", "all", "..!!!!", "Jai", "Shiv", "Shankar", "!!!"], "ner_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PERSON", "I-PERSON", "O"]}
{"id": 188, "tokens": ["#InsafianTheLosers", "Yeah", "but", "\"", "Haar", "Kay", "jeetnay", "Walay", "\"", "(", "moral", "victories", ")", "while", "Patwaris", "are", "\"", "Jeet", "Kay", "bhi", "Harnay", "Waly", "\""], "ner_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PERSON", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": 189, "tokens": ["RT", "@ksushma140", ":", "#DrMSG's", "Dance", "move", "for", "love", "charger", "movie", "version", "MSG", "Online", "Gurukul", "during", "#PiousBhandara", "https://t.co/L1Ue5HGpvM"], "ner_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": 190, "tokens": ["Marramay", "muqaddar", "ki", "kar", "do", "maula", "..."], "ner_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": 191, "tokens": ["@Gurmeetramrahim", "#MSGmissionHumanity", "Thank", "You", "Guruji", ".", "Good", "Morning", "&", "Lov", "You", ".", "Pita", "ji", "bless", "me", "for", "more", "sewa", "simran", ".", "https://t.co/EnUVUDW22A"], "ner_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": 192, "tokens": ["RT", "@htTweets", ":", "Pakistan", "militant", "groups", "role", "in", "#PathankotAttack", "decoded", ",", "(", "Reports", "@vinayak_ramesh", ")", "https://t.co/LUkMddRYY4", "https://t.co/SA"], "ner_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "B-PLACE", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": 193, "tokens": ["RT", "@abhijix", ":", "He", ":", "Hi", ",", "kaisi", "hai", "?", "She", ":", "Mast", ",", "tu", "bata", "He", ":", "Hmm", ",", "tu", "paragon", "..", "v2406", "@bhattkaran83", "@iambmane", "@pg27693", "@hbparmar211", "http://t.co/cOz"], "ner_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": 194, "tokens": ["I", "just", "realised", "aaj", "Mahashivratri", "hai", "!", "Apne", "Pandit", "ka", "hilltop", "mandir", "khula", "hoga", "aaj", "to", "@Filmbuff100", "@hennaav"], "ner_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PLACE", "I-PLACE", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": 195, "tokens": ["@firstpostin", "Shobha", "knows", "only", "one", "\"", "(", "Soniya", ")", "Gandhi", "\""], "ner_tags": ["O", "B-PERSON", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PERSON", "O", "B-PERSON", "O"]}
{"id": 196, "tokens": ["He", "who", "had", "wings", "of", "fire", ".", "He", "who", "ignited", "a", "billion", "minds", "and", "lives", "on", "in", "a", "zillion", "hearts", ".", "RIP", "@APJAbdulKalam", "#missileman", "#AbdulKalam"], "ner_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": 197, "tokens": ["#RailBudget2015", "@narendramodi", "Ye", "1st", "april", "se", "implement", "karne", "waale", "ho", "ya", "1st", "april", "fool", "day", "announcement", "ki", "kosis", "h"], "ner_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": 198, "tokens": ["RT", "@medhanarmada", ":", "Illegal", "sand", "mining", "continues", "unabated", "at", "Sardar", "Sarovar", "project", "in", "MP", ",", "green", "panel", "rues", ".", "https://t.co/s16qoM420E"], "ner_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PLACE", "I-PLACE", "O", "O", "B-PLACE", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": 199, "tokens": ["RT", "@taran_adarsh", ":", "#RRajkumar", "movie", "review", ":", "Doesn't", "work", ".", "It", "is", "Prabhu", "Dheva's", "weakest", "Hindi", "film", "to", "date", "!", "http://t.co/7PED6IdvXm"], "ner_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PERSON", "I-PERSON", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": 200, "tokens": ["@midwestmoviesus", "india", "lo", "avg", "os", "hit", "sir"], "ner_tags": ["O", "B-PLACE", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": 201, "tokens": ["Lalu", ":", "\"", "paida", "hi", "rajnigandha", "leke", "hua", "tha", "\"", "#RajnigandhaSixWordsStory", "Lalko", "se", "galti", "hou", "jati", "hai", "https://t.co/iHo1zAnpB6"], "ner_tags": ["B-PERSON", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": 202, "tokens": ["Rahul", "Dravid", "You're", "Our", "Lucky", "Charm", ":')", "#DDvKKR"], "ner_tags": ["B-PERSON", "I-PERSON", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": 203, "tokens": ["Mitsubishi", "should", "rename", "itself", "to", "chaarsobisi", ".", "https://t.co/HEEUSsTmg7"], "ner_tags": ["B-ORGANISATION", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": 204, "tokens": ["First", "Win", "give", "Too", "much", "hosala", "too", "Lahories", "#LahoreQalandars"], "ner_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": 205, "tokens": ["@Khabergaramhai", "Lol", "har", "koi", "yhi", "bolta", "hyn", "..", "End", "mein", "har", "ghar", "sw", "ek", "awaz", "ati", "H", "!", "Hamein", "tmse", "pyar", "h", "#PCB"], "ner_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": 206, "tokens": ["#RahulOnLeave", ".", "Bhailog", "India", "main", "hi", "he", ".", "Himalay", "gaya", "hei", "..", "to", "think"], "ner_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "B-PLACE", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PLACE", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": 207, "tokens": ["@SrBachchan", "RIP", "my", "cheeni", "kum", "sweetheart", "....."], "ner_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": 208, "tokens": ["#Fun", "#At", "#Beach", "#Collage", "#PicsArt", "P", ".", "Akhil", "@", "Marina", "Beach", ",", "Chennai", "-", "Tamilnadu", "http://t.co/RfMXaQvAYN"], "ner_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PERSON", "O", "B-PLACE", "I-PLACE", "O", "B-PLACE", "O", "B-PLACE", "O"]}
{"id": 209, "tokens": ["Kaale", "hai", "toh", "kya", "hua", "?", "Dilwale", "hain", ".", "@", "Emaar", "Boulevard", ",", "Downtown", "https://t.co/ux601C2lUf"], "ner_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PLACE", "I-PLACE", "O", "B-PLACE", "O"]}
{"id": 210, "tokens": ["zra", "#RahulOnLeave", "se", "puchiye", "pichle", "9", "mnths", "me", "#amethi", "me", "ky", "kaam", "kiya", "hai", ".", "Jawab", "dene", "k", "mamle", "me", "#Zero", "#WhereIsRahul", "aye", "usase", "to", "mla", "ki", "s"], "ner_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": 211, "tokens": ["Akhtar", "is", "like", "begaani", "shadi", "me", "abbdulha", "diwana", "....", "#IndvsPak"], "ner_tags": ["B-PERSON", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": 212, "tokens": ["@sejaljobanputra", "Kejriwal", "is", "alleging", "that", "Sonia", "Modi", "working", "together", "to", "s", "uttle", "#AgustaScam"], "ner_tags": ["O", "B-PERSON", "O", "O", "O", "B-PERSON", "B-PERSON", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": 213, "tokens": ["Can", "We", "Trend", "MAHASHIVRATRI/SHIVRATI", "KI", "SHUBHKAMNAYE", "In", "Hindi", "Tmrw", "?", "@missionbihar", "@yesiamsaffron", "@aditispeaks_", "@rss_org"], "ner_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": 214, "tokens": ["aaj", "to", "bohot", "khush", "hogi", "Soniya", "Gandhi", ",", "Rahul", "is", "finally", "trending", "in", "India", "...", "der", "aae", "but", "durust", "aae", "!!!", "#RahulOnLeave", "#WhereIsRahul"], "ner_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PERSON", "I-PERSON", "O", "B-PERSON", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PLACE", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": 215, "tokens": ["RT", "@rcmms", ":", "Shiv", "Bhakti", "ka", "ek", "hi", "pramaan", ",", "iss", "Mahashivatri", "doodh", "ka", "daan", "!", "Lets", "feed", "the", "hungry", "this", "Mahashivratri", ".", ":)", "#TheWhiteRevolution"], "ner_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "B-PERSON", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": 216, "tokens": ["Suresh", "Raina", "and", "Priyanka", "Chaudhary", "Marriage", "Photos", "More", "Pics", "at", ":", "http://t.co/CHlIqzqc1a", "#RainaKiShaadi", "@ImRaina", "http://t.co/794rg85iQO"], "ner_tags": ["B-PERSON", "I-PERSON", "O", "B-PERSON", "I-PERSON", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": 217, "tokens": ["#WIvZIM", "me", "agar", "Zimbabwe", "jeet", "jaati", "to", ",", "RaGa", "ka", "Empowerment", "waala", "dream", "poora", "ho", "jaata", "#WhereIsRahul", "#WhereIsRahulGandhi"], "ner_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "B-PLACE", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PERSON", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": 218, "tokens": ["Who's", "the", "abusive", "\"", "psychopath", "\"", "huh", "?", "https://t.co/d31WWxdEDx"], "ner_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": 219, "tokens": ["RT", "@IndianPrism", ":", "Can", "somone", "at", "Jadavpur", "Uni", "please", "confirm", "whether", "this", "report", "is", "genuine", "?", "Seems", "Mr", "@vivekagnihotri", "is", "circulating", "fake/", "du"], "ner_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PLACE", "I-PLACE", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": 220, "tokens": ["@FBkaBaap", "ya", "phir", "@cm_qaimalishah", "jesi", "mummy", "bn", "jata", "he", "..", "slam", "Photography", "https://t.co/ZTmVNQlgwv"], "ner_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": 221, "tokens": ["1", "Saal", "Pahle", ":", "Mujhe", "ganga", "maiyya", "ne", "bulaya", "hai", ".", "1", "Saal", "Baad", ":", "Ab", "agar", "aaya", "to", "bhigo", "bhigo", "ke", "......", "#Modi"], "ner_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": 222, "tokens": ["Do", "dilli", "wale", "out", "ho", "nahi", "rahe", ",", "aur", "inhe", "Kashmir", "chahiye", "BC", "-_-", "#IndvsPak"], "ner_tags": ["O", "B-PLACE", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PLACE", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": 223, "tokens": ["@Atheist_Club", ":", "#Hinduism", "is", "a", "sadak", "chhap", "religion", "#MahaShivRatri", "u", "drink", "bhaang", ",", "smk", "ganza", ",", "shame", ".", "@rsshukla62", "@taslimanasreen", "@THEdsaher"], "ner_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": 224, "tokens": ["@SANDEEPCOL", "@narendramodi", "Tune", "bola", "to", "samajh", "ho", "gaya", "sandy", "bhai", "..", "Raat", "bahut", "go", "gayee", "ja", "so", "ja", "..", "Nahi", "to", "bavala-panti", "karta", "rahega"], "ner_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": 225, "tokens": ["Swim", "swim", "#giabby", "excited", "@", "Shangri-La's", "Rasa", "Sentosa", "Resort", "&", "Spa", "https://t.co/bBk1e6H7jP"], "ner_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORGANISATION", "B-PLACE", "I-PLACE", "I-PLACE", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": 226, "tokens": [":", "LAST", "NIGHT", "MAHASHIVRATRI", "RUDRABHISHEK", ".....", "Pooja", "sampanna", "...", "JAI", "MAHADEV", "...", "http://t.co/7JScg0yY3l"], "ner_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PERSON", "I-PERSON", "O", "O", "B-PERSON", "O", "O"]}
{"id": 227, "tokens": ["RT", "@AdityaRajKaul", ":", "At", "the", "World", "Sufi", "Forum", ",", "New", "Delhi", ",", "organiser", "Syed", "Hazrat", "Ashaf", "tells", "me", ",", "Sufism", "counter", "to", "radical", "Islamist", "terror", ".", "htt"], "ner_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORGANISATION", "I-ORGANISATION", "I-ORGANISATION", "O", "B-PLACE", "I-PLACE", "O", "O", "B-PERSON", "I-PERSON", "I-PERSON", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": 228, "tokens": ["In", "morning", "listening", "Shiv", "Mahimn", "Shtotra", "&", "Shiv", "Tandav", "Shtotra", "sung", "by", "Shri", ".", "Ramesh", "Oza", "#MahaShivratri"], "ner_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "B-PERSON", "O", "O", "O", "B-PERSON", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PERSON", "I-PERSON", "O"]}
{"id": 229, "tokens": ["RT", "@amitsultania11", ":", "One", "side", "bajrangi", "baahijan", "house", "full", "on", "the", "other", "side", "baahubali", "also", "house", "full", "today", "at", "rewari", "BMG", "mall", "Awesome"], "ner_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PLACE", "I-PLACE", "I-PLACE", "O"]}
{"id": 230, "tokens": ["Shiv", "Tandava", "Stotra", "-", "Ravana's", "hymn", "of", "praise", "for", "Shiv", "https://t.co/66afoUr8xY", "#MahaShivratri"], "ner_tags": ["B-PERSON", "O", "O", "O", "B-PERSON", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PERSON", "O", "O"]}
{"id": 231, "tokens": ["@Abdullahbaltit", "Rangers", "ki", "raid", "karaden", "inpe", ".", "Poori", "qoum", "pe", "ehsaan", "hoga", "."], "ner_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": 232, "tokens": ["Kyu", "bhagwan", "kyu", ".", "Hamare", "saath", "hi", "kyu", "#INDvAUS", "e", ":", "BSF", "troops", "http://t.co/gqN1mGkChA"], "ner_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORGANISATION", "O", "O"]}
{"id": 233, "tokens": ["\"", "@TimesNow", ":", "Cigarette", ",", "pan", "masala", "to", "be", "costlier", ":", "FM", "Arun", "Jaitley", "#SuperBudget", "\"", "Outrage", "ega", ".", "Aap", "AK", "ko", "Punjab", "bhejke", "khud", "Delhi", "ke", "CM", "banjao", "."], "ner_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PERSON", "I-PERSON", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PERSON", "O", "B-PLACE", "O", "O", "B-PLACE", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": 234, "tokens": ["Believe", "na", "ho", "to", "wikipedia", "me", "Awards", "section", "padh", "le", "#ConfusionKaEnd", "#SRKDonates1crToChennai", "#ISupportDelhiOddEven", "https://t.co/eegdts4Kf8"], "ner_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORGANISATION", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": 235, "tokens": ["RT", "@TanuInsan", ":", "@Gurmeetramrahim", "@samachar_plus", "@6", "#HeroNo1BRR", "thanku", "guru", "ji", "PTI", "chairman", "criticis", "...", "https://t.co/l9HbDy1hIW", "#etribune"], "ner_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": 236, "tokens": ["@amitava258", "I", "think", "Vipul", "was", "dropped", "...", "Aankhen", "2", "will", "probably", "be", "directed", "by", "Aneez", "Bazmi"], "ner_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "B-PERSON", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PERSON", "I-PERSON"]}
{"id": 237, "tokens": ["RT", "@abhilash_jagtap", ":", "Happy", "Birthday", "to", "most", "talented", "batsman", "of", "current", "era", "Roooohit", "@ImRo45", "#HappyBirthdayHitman"], "ner_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PERSON", "O", "O"]}
{"id": 238, "tokens": ["RT", "@Dishasatra", ":", "Rahul", "Gandhi's", "speeches", "be", "like", "https://t.co/GoLS2bXSmL"], "ner_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "B-PERSON", "I-PERSON", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": 239, "tokens": ["@dhoni_maniac", "@gauravindoriya", "@SachinmOfficial", "@TeamChak", "@Rowdy_Nik", "aaj", "to", "jashnn", "ho", "rha", "h", "Jaipur", "mein"], "ner_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PLACE", "O"]}
{"id": 240, "tokens": ["Perfect", "railway", "budget", "ever", "#BudgetBT", "#", "#RailBudget2015", "#IndianRailways", "@abpnewstv", "@aajtakki", "to", "jal", "gyi", ",", "Pata", "ni", "konsa", "mulk", "h", "inka"], "ner_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": 241, "tokens": ["Post", "on", "@Quora", "by", "Shubham", "Khandelwal", ":", "Alive", "Without", "you", "https://t.co/3wM201NSeH"], "ner_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PERSON", "I-PERSON", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": 242, "tokens": ["RT", "@Bluemagicboxes", ":", "The", "actual", "quote", "vs", ".", "Tribune", "reporting", ".", "Clapping", "hojaye", "ek", "baar", ".", "https://t.co/2YcsjRpgRk"], "ner_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORGANISATION", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": 243, "tokens": ["@TajinderBagga", "Sabse", "jyada", "to", "hamara", "hai", ",", "koi", "bole", "kaha", "se", "ho", "ham", "bole", "UP", "se", "to", "bolte", "haan", "matlab", "Bihari", "ho", ".", "Nitish", "ko", "kyu", "vote", "kiya", "..", "Sigh", "!"], "ner_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PLACE", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PERSON", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": 244, "tokens": ["Suresh", "Prabhu's", "reaction", "on", "Indian", "Railways", "\"", "hey", "prabhu", "kaise", "hoga", "ye", "sab", "\"", "@RailMinIndia", "@sureshpprabhu", "#RailBudget2015", "#RailwayBudget"], "ner_tags": ["B-PERSON", "I-PERSON", "O", "O", "B-ORGANISATION", "I-ORGANISATION", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": 245, "tokens": ["RT", "@santanu_maji9", ":", "Last", "EID", "pic", "!", "Aamir", "and", "Koyla", "Karkhana", "Ka", "Majdoor", "http://t.co/1zctb9vG3d"], "ner_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PERSON", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": 246, "tokens": ["Waise", "to", "@ArvindKejriwal", "Sirf", "Sonia/Sisodia/Sanjay", "Ki", "hi", "sunte", "h", "par", "is", "bar", "@chetan_bhagat", "Ki", "sun", "li", "aur", "#AugustaWestland", "p", "muh", "kholdiya", "wah"], "ner_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PERSON", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": 247, "tokens": ["Roger's", "potentialpathin", "Madrid", "open", ":", "1R", ":", "Bye", "2R", ":", "Mahut", "or", "Sousa", "3R", ":", "Thiem", "QF", ":", "Rafa", "SF", ":", "Murray", "Final", ":", "Novak", "#AllezRoger"], "ner_tags": ["B-PERSON", "O", "B-PLACE", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PERSON", "O", "B-PERSON", "O", "O", "B-PERSON", "O", "O", "B-PERSON", "O", "O", "B-PERSON", "O", "O", "B-PERSON", "O"]}
{"id": 248, "tokens": ["'", "Bank", "jaane", "ke", "liye", "bank", "jaane", "ki", "kya", "zaroorat", "?", "'", "#AwesomeLogic", "#AxisBankAd"], "ner_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": 249, "tokens": ["RT", "@Dharanishanthi", ":", "RT", "@SankalpSharan", ":", "Rail", "research", "institute", "will", "open", "@", "IIT", "BHU", ",", "kanpur", "#RailBudget2015", "bt", "no", "one", "sees", "this", "#RespectResea"], "ner_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORGANISATION", "I-ORGANISATION", "I-ORGANISATION", "O", "O", "O", "B-PLACE", "I-PLACE", "O", "B-PLACE", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": 250, "tokens": ["Happy", "Mahashivratri", "..", "Om", "Ganeshay", "namah", "..", "Om", "Umashankar", "Namah", "..", "Om", "Namo", "Shivay", "..", "http://t.co/B1h4lJQwIn"], "ner_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PERSON", "O", "O", "O", "B-PERSON", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": 251, "tokens": ["Kis", "Kisko", "Pyaar", "Karoon", "-", "Official", "Trailer", "-", "Kapil", "Sharma", ",", "Arbaaz", "Khan", ",", "Eli", "Avram", "&", "Manjari", "Phadnis", "http://t.co/XDhFJyi8jQ"], "ner_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PERSON", "I-PERSON", "O", "B-PERSON", "I-PERSON", "O", "B-PERSON", "I-PERSON", "O", "B-PERSON", "I-PERSON", "O"]}
{"id": 252, "tokens": ["@Gurmeetramrahim", "#MSGsocialWelfare", "dhan", "dhan", "satguru", "tera", "hi", "aasra", "@@", "pitaji", "gud", "morning"], "ner_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PERSON", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": 253, "tokens": ["@kritisanon", "aap", "bolo", "aur", "miss", "kr", "jau", "...", "no", "way"], "ner_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": 254, "tokens": ["@RabiaAnumm", "Phir", "bhi", "Jeetega", "to", "India", "hi", ":)", "Kuch", "bhi", "karlo", ":D", "#IndvsPak", "#IndiaWins", "#CWC15"], "ner_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PLACE", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": 255, "tokens": ["RT", "@ZoomTV", ":", "Post", "Bajirao", "success", "Ranveer", "Singh", "now", "charges", "as", "much", "as", "Shah", "Rukh", "Khan", "for", "performances", "https://t.co/itB7VhUJRs"], "ner_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PERSON", "O", "B-PERSON", "I-PERSON", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PERSON", "I-PERSON", "I-PERSON", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": 256, "tokens": ["RT", "@65thakursahab", ":", "Today", "is", "the", "birth", "anniversary", "of", "Maharana", "Pratap", ",", "whose", "bravery", "&", "indomitable", "spirit", "doesn't", "fail", "to", "inspire", "even", "today", "."], "ner_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PERSON", "I-PERSON", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": 257, "tokens": ["RT", "@ndtv", ":", "#SaveWaterSaveLives", "|", "Nana", "Patekar", "on", "Marathwada", "drought", "https://t.co/apVacsSquk", "ross", "india", "..", "sick", "Arnab", "Goswami", "."], "ner_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PERSON", "I-PERSON", "O", "B-PLACE", "O", "O", "O", "B-PLACE", "O", "O", "B-PERSON", "I-PERSON", "O"]}
{"id": 258, "tokens": ["RT", "@Babu_Bhaiyaa", ":", "This", "outcry", "by", "Sonia", "G", "is", "her", "way", "of", "saying-Kya", "Modi", "ji", "!", "Hum", "yahan", "Opposition", "mai", "baith", "kr", "bhi", "scam", "kr", "sakte", "hain", ".", "Tum", "Gov"], "ner_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PERSON", "I-PERSON", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PERSON", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": 259, "tokens": ["@madhurahnaikHappyMahaShivratriCuteMadhura", "Naik", "Ji", "Har", "Har", "MahaDev"], "ner_tags": ["O", "B-PERSON", "I-PERSON", "O", "O", "B-PERSON"]}
{"id": 260, "tokens": ["Shit", "Yaar", "...", "clean", "sweep", "nahi", "kar", "paya-", "AK", "..", "#AAPSweep", "#AAPStorm", "#DelhiDecides", "#dillikiski"], "ner_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": 261, "tokens": ["RT", "@usha_khokhar", ":", "Pakistan", "ke", "liye", "Venue", "Change", "hua", "Menu", "nahi", "..", "Mili", "haar", "hi", "#IndvsPak"], "ner_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "B-PLACE", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": 262, "tokens": ["#", "_", "_", "ek", "larki", "ko", "dekha", "to", "aisa", "laga"], "ner_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": 263, "tokens": ["PIB_India", "#UHF", "DEMUs", "will", "be", "converted", "to", "dual", "fuel", "(", "CNG/Diesel", ")", ":", "sureshpprabhu", "#RailBudget2015"], "ner_tags": ["B-ORGANISATION", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PERSON", "O"]}
{"id": 264, "tokens": ["RT", "@HaramiParindey", ":", "Virat", "Kohli", "is", "the", "only", "person", "who", "can", "chase", "his", "dreams", "."], "ner_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "B-PERSON", "I-PERSON", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": 265, "tokens": ["@DarshanBangera", "@feminamissindia", "@ColorsTV", "haha", "!", "Hota", "hai", "hota", "hai", ".."], "ner_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": 266, "tokens": ["\"", "@ATSBB", ":", "Rithvik", "Aur", "Asha", "ka", "Havan", "khas", "Mahashivratri", "par", "..", "dekhiyega", "zarur", "sirf", "SBB", "me", "2.30", "Baje", "http://t.co/9daj7A0mrn", "\"", "Omg"], "ner_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "B-PERSON", "O", "B-PERSON", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": 267, "tokens": ["RT", "@ClassicallyWild", ":", "Sharmaji", "ka", "beta", "isn't", "performing", ".", "Kohli", "ji", "ke", "bete", "ho", "dekhlo"], "ner_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "B-PERSON", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PERSON", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": 268, "tokens": ["@Gurmeetramrahim", "#MSG", "Salutes", "papaji", "good", "morning", "parivar", "ko", "sewa", "simran", "parmarth", "nd", "man", "se", "larne", "ka", "bal", "do", "."], "ner_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": 269, "tokens": ["Ghar", "beth", "Kay", "..", "Ki", "banay", "ga", "es", "mulak", "da", ".", "#", "_", "_"], "ner_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": 270, "tokens": ["Remembered", "Marriage", "of", "Shakti", "in", "Munimji", ".", "O", "Shivji", "Bihane", "Chale", "by", "Hemant", "Kumar", ".", "https://t.co/AUINRKpdWp", "#", "#MahaShivratri"], "ner_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "B-PERSON", "O", "B-PLACE", "O", "O", "B-PERSON", "O", "O", "O", "B-PERSON", "I-PERSON", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": 271, "tokens": ["#AIB", "Roast", "Roster", "Roastest", "..!!", "Indeed", "it", "was", "Roastest", "..!!", "Poor", "Ranveer", "n", "Arjun", ":D"], "ner_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PERSON", "O", "B-PERSON", "O"]}
{"id": 272, "tokens": ["RT", "@shalinit_6", ":", "@AnupamPkher", "BTW", "aapko", "kisne", "nishkasit", "kiya", "?", "aap", "to", "pehle", "shimla", ",", "phir", "lucknow", "aur", "ab", "bombay", "me", "rehte", "ho", "...", "hadd", "hai", "jhut", "boln"], "ner_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PLACE", "O", "O", "B-PLACE", "O", "O", "B-PLACE", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": 274, "tokens": ["agar", "#notebandi", "ke", "time", "political", "party", "bhi", "#rti", "ke", "daayre", "me", "aa", "jati", "to", "#sukmaattack", "#kashmir", "me", "patthar", "attack", "na", "hote", "@PMOIndia"], "ner_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORGANISATION", "I-ORGANISATION", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": 275, "tokens": ["#notebandi", "ke", "baad", "bhi", "aam", "janta", "ke", "#bankaccount", "me", "15", "laakh", "rs", "nahi", "aaye", "@PMOIndia", "akele", "sabka", "paisa", "kaise", "ghot", "sakte", "hain", "@sambitswaraj"], "ner_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORGANISATION", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": 276, "tokens": ["Masterstroke", "to", "Modiji", "ne", "usi", "din", "maar", "diya", "tha", "jab", "#notebandi", "ki", "thi", "0"], "ner_tags": ["O", "O", "B-PERSON", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": 277, "tokens": ["Jin", "logon", "ko", "desh", "ke", "President", "aur", "PM", "tak", "ka", "naam", "nahi", "pata", "woh", "log", "bhi", "GST", "pe", "Chai ", "par", "charcha", "kar", "rahein", "hain.", "#GST", "#GSTForNewIndia"], "ner_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "B-ORGANISATION", "O", "B-PERSON", "O", "B-PERSON", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": 278, "tokens": ["petrol", ",", "alcohol", ",", "tobacco", "par", "GST", "Kyo", "nahi", "?", "kya", "iska", "liya", "desh", "1", "nahi", "hai", "?", "pata", "hai", "answer", "nahi", "milaga", "?", "phir", "bhe", "!!", "#GST"], "ner_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORGANISATION", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": 280, "tokens": ["Hindustan", "ki", "aisi", "takdeer", "likh", "maula", ",", "Ki", "log", "Sanskrit", "me", "allah", "aur", "Urdu", "me", "ram", "likhe", "...."], "ner_tags": ["B-PLACE", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PERSON", "O", "O"]}
{"id": 281, "tokens": ["congress", "bol", "rahi", "hai", "packed", "to", "egg", "bhi", "hai", "use", "kyu", "0%", "par", "rakha", "hua", "hai", "use", "bhi", "5%", "me", "dalo", "#GST"], "ner_tags": ["B-ORGANISATION", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": 282, "tokens": ["Jb", "ap", "unmarried", "hote", "hu", "toh", "apni", "salry", "mai", "apni", "Maa,", "bhai,", "behan", "ko", "hisa", "dete", "hu", "AUR", "shadi", "k", "baad", "sb", "kuch", "biwi", "ko", "dna", "padta", "hai", "Yh", "hai", "#GST"], "ner_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": 285, "tokens": ["#INDvWI", "Aaj", "to", "india", "team", "aur", "dhoni", "per", "bhi", "#GST", "ka", "asar", "dikh", "rha", "h"], "ner_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "B-PLACE", "O", "O", "B-PERSON", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": 286, "tokens": ["Yaha", "sab", "bol", "rahe", "Hai", "ki", "#GST", "Samajh", "nhi", "aa", "rha...", "And", "m", "like", "k", "aaj", "tak", "kaunsa", "tax", "Samajh", "aaya", "mujhe", "Jo", "ye", "aayega"], "ner_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": 287, "tokens": ["Aaj", "ek", "gadget", "aur", "kharid", "lo..", "Aaj", "bazaar", "se", "saari", "sabziyaan", "aur", "baaki", "ghar", "ka", "saamaan", "le", "lo..", "Aaj!", "Kya", "pata", "kal", "ho", "na", "ho!!!", "#GST"], "ner_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": 288, "tokens": ["Sab", "cahate", "hai", "des", "ka", "bikash", "ho", "lekin", "jab", "contribution", "ke", "bat", "aye", "mhu", "pherna", "adat", "sa", "hogaya", "hai", "#GST"], "ner_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": 289, "tokens": ["Are", "yaar", "#GST", "nsi", "ho", "gya", "koi", "theory", "ho", "gai", "smajh", "hi", "nai", "aa", "rha"], "ner_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": 290, "tokens": ["Ek ", "#GST", "feik", "ke", "maarenge", "ki", "bhool", "jaaoge", "ki", "karcha", "kahaan", "karna", "hai", "aur", "save", "kahaan", "karna", "hai.."], "ner_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": 291, "tokens": ["\"", "@sri50", ":", "#MahaShivratri", "today", ".", "Hara", "Hara", "Mahadev", ".", "\"", "Ivarkum", "therichirukku", "ha", "ha", "..", "@rj_janakarajan", "@shyamkkumar"], "ner_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PERSON", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": 292, "tokens": ["July", "me", "paida", "huwe", "bache", "Expensive", "hi", "hote", "hai", "#GST", "to", "ab", "aaya", "hai"], "ner_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": 293, "tokens": ["Raat", "12", "baje", "ke", "baad", "GHANTA", "baja", "ke", "#GST", "implement", "hoga", "toh", "samajh", "gaye", "na", "ke", "kya", "samaj", "mein", "aane", "wala", "hai", "Lol."], "ner_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": 295, "tokens": ["#gstrollout", "kisi", "ko", "problems", "ho", "ya", "na", "ho", "@INCIndia", "ko", "ye", "problem", "hai", "ki", "#GST", "12", "baje", "raat", "ko", "kyu", "laagu", "ho", "raha", "hai...", "Waah", "re", "raajneeti"], "ner_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": 298, "tokens": ["30", "June", "ko", "aadhi", "raat", "Parliament", "ke", "central", "hall", "mein", "#GST", "ko", "le", "kar", "jo", "jashn", "manaya", "ja", "rha", "h,", "hamari", "party", "usme", "shaamil", "nahi", "hogi:", "GN", "Azad"], "ner_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": 299, "tokens": ["Aapki", "party", "sirf", "aadhi", "raat", "ko", "aatankiyon", "ki", "faansi", "maaf", "karwane", "jaati", "hai", "ya", "Mass", "Murderer", "Anderson", "ko", "desh", "se", "bhagane"], "ner_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORGANISATION", "O", "O"]}
{"id": 300, "tokens": ["Are", "bhai", "jab", "VAT", "hum", "de", "rhe,", "#GST", "hum", "consumer", "se", "rhe", "toh", "ye", "dukan", "wale", "kyu", "hartal", "pe", "baithe", "hai?"], "ner_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": 302, "tokens": ["\"", "Rahul", "Gandhi", ",", "joke", "to", "suna", "hoga", "?", "\"", "#TwistedBollywoodDialogues", "#RahulOnLeave", "#WhereIsRahul"], "ner_tags": ["O", "B-PERSON", "I-PERSON", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": 303, "tokens": ["Atleast", "Unhe", "pata", "hona", "Chahiye", "#GST", "ke", "Basic", "rules", "ke", "bare", "me", ",Nahi", "toh", "Kuch", "log", "hamari", "Sarkar", "ke", "bare", "Galat", "Message", "De", "rahe", "Hai", "traders", "ko"], "ner_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": 306, "tokens": ["Sara", "prachar,", "Bhavya", "samaroh", "ye", "sab", "to", "theek", "hai,", "lekin", "GST", "ke", "liye", "technical", "support", "taiyyar", "nahi", "hai", "to", "use", "laagu", "kaise", "karoge?", "#GST", "#PMO"], "ner_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": 307, "tokens": ["you", "are", "in", "shock", "....", "hawaiyan", "udd", "gyi", "....", "#notebandi", "chal", "gya", "0", "janta", "Ka", "thapad", "pad", "gya", "...", "aap", "ab", "chaplusi", "par", "na", "Utar", "jaiyega"], "ner_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": 308, "tokens": ["We", "can", "save", "and", "educate", "our", "“Beti”", "(Beti", "Bachai,Beti", "Padai)", "@mlkhattar", "lekin", "sir", "aap", "unhe", "darindo", "se", "toh", "bachao.", "#Nirbhaya", "#DarindoSeBachaoKanoonLao"], "ner_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": 310, "tokens": ["rape", "ki", "sazaa", "kuch", "ulemaa", "k", "nazdeek", "1", "bazu", "aur", "1", "taang", "katna", "bhi", "ho", "sakti", "ha.", "Case", "par", "depend", "karta", "ha"], "ner_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": 311, "tokens": ["koi", "chori", "krta", "h", "to", "uske", "haat", "kaatwa", "diye", "jaaye", "or", "agr", "koi", "rape", "krta", "h", "to", "uski", "mardaangi", "ka", "subut", "hi", "ktwa", "diya", "jaaye", "or", "beech", "sadak", "pr", "latka", "kr", "phaansi", "honi", "chahye.."], "ner_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": 313, "tokens": ["Lag", "rha", "hai", "aaj", "Rahul", "Gandhi", "Zimbabwe", "ka", "Support", "kr", "rhe", "the", ".", "#WhereIsRahulGandhi", "#WhereIsRahul"], "ner_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PERSON", "I-PERSON", "B-PLACE", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": 314, "tokens": ["rape", "karne", "balo", "ko", "15", "year", "ki", "saja", "deni", "chahiye"], "ner_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": 315, "tokens": ["Zara", "si", "bhi", "sharam", "hai", "to", "unko", "gale", "lagao", "jin", "choti", "choti", "betiyo", "Ko", "Hariyana", "rape", "karke", "maar", "diya", "Gaya", "ya", "marne", "k", "liye", "chod", "diya", "Gaya", "0"], "ner_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PLACE", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": 317, "tokens": ["Sab", "par", "ab", "janata", "janardan", "ka", "faisala", "...", "Jaldi", "sona", "hai", "shubha", "8", "baje", "hamare", "desh", "ke", "future", "ka", "pata", "lagega", "0", "#notebandi", "ka", "jawab"], "ner_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "B-ORGANISATION", "I-ORGANISATION", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORGANISATION", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": 318, "tokens": ["Kash", "ke", "teen", "talaq", "bill", "pas", "ho", "jata", "to", "Aaj", "in", "bachiyun", "ka", "Gang", "Rape", "Nahi", "hota", "!!!!!!!"], "ner_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": 320, "tokens": ["Mallab", "nirbhaya", "ki", "headline", "isliye", "bani", "qki", "WO", "general", "thi", "?"], "ner_tags": ["O", "B-PERSON", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": 321, "tokens": ["Abe", "kutte", "Tum", "log", "Hindu", "Muslim", "karte", "ho", "saboot", "shambhu", "regar", "ko", "Hinduon", "ka", "neta", "kahan", "Jo", "behan", "bolkar", "ladki", "ka", "rape", "karta", "tha", "bikau", "ho", "be"], "ner_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORGANISATION", "B-ORGANISATION", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORGANISATION", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": 322, "tokens": ["Shambhulal", "ragar", "khud", "ki", "bahen", "rape", "karta", "tha", "uska", "pata", "afrajul", "ko", "thi", "rang", "de", "diya", "jo", "chal", "raha", "hai", "desh", "men", "nafrat", "ka"], "ner_tags": ["B-PERSON", "I-PERSON", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORGANISATION", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": 323, "tokens": ["Rape", "ko", "support", "nahi", "Karna", "chahiye", "jahe", "wo", "koi", "bhi", "ho"], "ner_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": 324, "tokens": ["Are", "you", "talking", "about", "Sonia", "Gandhi's", "work", "schedule", "in", "the", "future", "??", "#WomensDay", "https://t.co/G5XnpPtj46"], "ner_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PERSON", "I-PERSON", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": 325, "tokens": ["Per", "ek", "baat", "hai", "samajwadi", "NE", "abhi", "bhi", "gayatri", "ko", "party", "se", "nahi", "nikala"], "ner_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORGANISATION", "O", "O", "O", "B-PERSON", "O", "B-ORGANISATION", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": 326, "tokens": ["@MamataOfficial", "@sardanarohit", "Woh", "Jo", "#NoteBandi", "k", "agst", "#AamaranAnshan", "karne", "waale", "the", "uska", "kya", "hua", "...", "Mare", "nahin", "ab", "tak"], "ner_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": 327, "tokens": ["Jab", "8", "year", "ki", "aayesha", "Ka", "rape", "hua", "tab", "Porki", "kaha", "mar", "gye", "the", ".."], "ner_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PERSON", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PERSON", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": 328, "tokens": ["Sir", "ji", "aap", "ka", "jan", "man", "to", "accha", "lagta", "hai", "per", "ek", "din", "me", "3", "rape", "hua", "hai", "haryana", "me", "koi", "MEDIA", "abhi", "tak", "nahi", "dikha", "rhi", "hai", "sub", "ke", "sub", "abhi", "modi", "ji", "ki", "jhappi", "per", "debate", "kar", "rhe", "hai", "hai"], "ner_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PLACE", "O", "O", "B-ORGANISATION", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PERSON", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": 329, "tokens": ["Jignesh", "time", "has", "come", "to", "raise", "voice", "against", "rape", "scandals", "hope", "you", "will", "agree", "with", "me", "that", "Jis", "desh", "me", "Maa", "Behan", "Beti", "Bahu", "surakshit", "nahi", "hai", "us", "desh", "ka", "P.M.", "56", "inch", "ki", "chaati", "ka", "achar", "dalenge."], "ner_tags": ["B-PERSON", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORGANISATION", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORGANISATION", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
